Take me back to the ground
'Cause girl, you look fine as hell (fine as hell)
I'm not easily distracted
But you're acting like a magnet
You pull me in
I'll be puttin' on a suit
Be tip toeing to you
If you're down for it
We got nothing else to do
And nothing else to lose
And I'm down for this
If you're in the mood
We can take it to the moon
Just like a movie scene
Table for two
No need to be fed
I want you instead
If you're in the mood
We can tip toe to the moon
Hold up, yeah
Tell my friends to pinch me hard
'Cause it couldn't be real (this can't be real)
Is this a dream I'm living
Lord help me, please
'Cause I can't get over you
I'll be putting on a suit
Be tip toeing to you
If you're down for it
We got nothing else to do
And nothing else to lose
And I'm down for this
Are you down for this?
If you're in the mood
We can take it to the moon
Just like a movie scene
Table for two
No need to be fed
I want you instead
If you're in the mood
We can tip toe to the moon
We can take it to the moon (take it to the moon)
Just like a movie scene
Table for two (table for two)
No need to be fed
I want you instead (tip toe to the moon)
If you're in the mood
We can tip toe to the moon
Tip toe, tip toe, tip toe, tip toe, tip toe, tip toe